Please support my friend 权权人button peach
Good morning
Good morning.
I didn't expect to see you here today.
Yes, from the Tohoku region.
Oh, oh, oh, oh!
What is it?
We've got a corporate project.
Oh, my God!
Corporate projects.
A very famous company in Miyagi Prefecture
Ishinomaki Fisheries
We are here at Ishinomaki Fisheries' direct sales factory!
Yay, here we are!
Today, we're going to take a tour of the factory, and I'd like to call our cheerleader for today.
Let's call the person in charge of today's tour.
Good morning!
How do you do?
How did you hear about us?
We've been thinking about this project a lot.
We have the most momentum in Tohoku.
You're welcome.
We'll be happy to help you.
Thank you very much.
So, I'll take you to the office and we'll go inside.
Let's go.
Let's go!
Let's go inside.
It's 6 degrees and 5 minutes.
We're in the 6 degrees 1st direct sales area, which is a two-tiered structure.
On this floor, they sell frozen products.
The boulevard is a Fellat, which is a rimination of frozen products.
The upper fence is also a direct sales place, so it was a little cheaper than Kokura good!
Can
Matt bout
Sake. You are playing with customers to match the sake.
I see.
This is a local sake, but I made this together with a sake shop in Ishinomaki.
Sake that goes well with whale.
Sake that goes well with whale? What does it taste like?
I heard that you can drink it now.
Yes, it is. Enjoy it. You should try it, too.
It's amazing.
And the back.
Oh, wow.
Whale! Whale! Whale!
A whale?
Yes, a whale.
It's a whale that we've been doing since Tokyo.
Oh, you've been able to put it in since long time ago.
Yes, since long ago.
That's great.
And then there's the small fish type things like this.
Oh, I love this kind of thing.
Oh, yes.
White.
Wow, I'm getting mackerel.
What is it? Can I...?
I'm gonna get mackerel.
It's good, isn't it? It's a new smell.
Is the tongue of a cow called "gyutan" or "gyutan"?
Whale's tongue has a name, too: sabazuri.
Wow, that's great.
Amazing.
Really? I'm so happy.
Let's buy it.
That's great.
Yes.
Oh, wow.
The former mackerel is amazing.
It's true.
It's decorated.
Once again, we are displaying all the canned goods we make at our company.
We finally have over 40 kinds now.
Forty kinds?
That's amazing.
Before the earthquake, there were a few more varieties.
We were able to spread the product lineup from there.
But at first, we were only able to produce about 10 varieties.
At last, we are finally getting back to where we were before the earthquake.
It's amazing.
It's full of history, isn't it?
History.
The most popular one is this gold leaf mackerel.
Oh, it looks delicious.
Looks delicious.
The standard is boiled in water, isn't it?
After all, it's Ishinomaki, isn't it? Boiled in water.
It's delicious, isn't it?
I'm sure.
My company has a fish market in Ishinomaki.
The trucks are less than 3 minutes away from the market.
It's amazing.
So the fish caught in the morning will be ready to eat as soon as possible, and the family will keep them.
They keep them with the family.
They are fresh.
It's there, isn't it?
There is that, isn't there?There it is, isn't there?
There are all kinds of things.
There are many different kinds, so if that's the case, I'll give you a little guess for each one.
I'll give you a little guess for each one.
Oh, you don't mind?
Let's find out.
I'm lost.
There are 40 kinds.
What is this one called?
This one is called "Sunoko.
Sunoko?
Yes.
There is this striped part.
This striped part is the part where the oil really sticks.
It's absolutely delicious.
So you can eat that part?
Yes, it is.
But only about 3% of all large whales can be caught.
I want you to try it. I want you to try it.
It goes well with sake.
I want to come back. I want to go back.
Here it is. Sardines with soy sauce.
Absolutely delicious.
It is said to be a seasonal flavor produced in Sanriku in limited quantities.
I'm on the fence about it.
I'm lost.
A popular product that won the Prime Minister's Award.
I'm so confused.
I'm going to choose this one.
King Salmon Bone. Mizuri with bone.
I'll choose this one.
Because the salmon looks delicious.
The color is also very Hikaru-like.
Indeed.
Bamboo shell?
Bamboo shell.
I'll have this tuna meat.
Precious meat. And it's also good for women.
This is ?
A woman is a woman.
Yo!
I ate it.
I got a new guess.
A guess.
So, this is a direct sales place, but we have a factory together.
Today, I was told that the factory where tanzumi is made is also open to the public.
So I would like to move on to that factory.
Thank you very much.
We will now move on.
Let's go!
Guess what.
We've arrived at the factory.
Yay!
Thank you very much.
This time, it's quite a bit, reminds me of when I was a little girl.
May I see something?
Of course.
Thank you very much.
This is the only place in all of Japan's food factories
Of all the food factories in Japan.
This is the only factory in Japan that you can see from the aisle.
Indeed! I've never seen this before.
What kind of process is this?
This is the near end of the canning process.
This is the process of closing the lid while allowing the canned food with sauce inside to air out.
This is the process of closing the lid while allowing air to escape from the canned food with sauce inside.
The factory tour is closed to the public at this Corona factory now.
But when it was originally open to the public, it was a tour course for nearby elementary and junior high schools.
But when it was originally open to the public, it was also offered as a field trip course for nearby elementary and junior high schools.
That's why it's so impressive.
The people in the back are the ones who came to see the tour.
There are also explanations and so on.
Now we're making eye contact.
I wonder where they are.
It's coming out.
For the first time.
Oh, my God, he showed me.
Is this a sea eel?
It's a sea eel.
Oh, my God.
That's great.
Thank you very much.
That's before Sfanet.
Before Sfanette.
That's right.
It's steaming, so it's about the size of a tour.
But it doesn't have any flavor yet.
That's a rare video.
I've seen it.
I've known him for a long time.
I've never seen him smile like that.
I'm so glad I pulled that out of him.
It's such a sudden change.
When the current lineup gets full.
When the current one fills up, we'll take it down a notch, cut another sheet, and take it down a notch.
We'll fill it up this way.
By the time it gets to the customer
about a month or three months before it goes to the customer.
And then we sell them.
Bye-bye.Bye-bye.
Gentle
So sweet.
Did you wave that much?
You scared me.
Thank you so much.
I'm not in the mood for this.
I gave you a new product.
New product?
I want you to try it.
You don't mind?
Thank you.
Let's go over there.
Thank you very much.
So.
I'd like to give you all a chance to try our new canned food.
I'd like you all to try some of the new canned food.
I'm going to blindfold you and you're going to eat it.
I'd like you all to guess what that canned food is.
I'd like to do a video in which
I'm going to do a video in which I blindfold you and ask you to guess what the canned food is.
I'm going to bring it in front of you.
So I'm going to bring it in front of you, and you're going to blindfold yourselves and wait.
You're not allowed to look.
Would you like to try a bite before we do the special quiz?
Yes, sir.
Yum!
I love it! Yum!
Was it good?
Oh, it's good!
It's so good!
It's amazing! It's amazing!
Delicious!
Isn't that Miyaki's wife? She's like...
She's a cat.
Miyaki is his wife.
I'll do my best to create it there.
I see.
Hey.
Let's start with Ritsuki.
Okay.
Hmm?
Well? Do you think you can understand it?
What? Isn't that a fish?
Fish?
I know fish!
Yes, sir!
What?
How's that?
Okay, next.
Kiste.
What's this?
Hmm?
Mmm?
It's sweet.
It's pretty thick.
Okay, let's see who can tell by a show of hands.
This is delicious.
Wait, what? What is it?
What did Elle eat?
What? It's disgusting.
It was delicious.
It was so good, I really want some rice.
It's meat.
Yes, of course.
What did it taste like?
Miso.
Miso?
Can I guess?
Yes, ma'am.
Yes, sir.
Sardines in miso.
No, you don't have sardines.
Is that what you mean? Do you have mackerel simmered in miso?
Saba no miso ni nimono (mackerel simmered in miso)?
No, wait!
Beef tongue curry.
No, it's not.
No, it's not. I thought it might be.
It's surprisingly clear, but it's simmered in miso.
Saba no Miso Nimono (mackerel stewed in miso).
No, but this is Ishinomaki, right? Ishinomaki Fisheries. Isn't that what Ishinomaki is famous for?
Persimmon? No, sir.
Sea squirts?
What?
Hoya cooked in miso?
No, sir.
Sea squirt in soy sauce? No, sir.
Simmered sea squirt? Correct.
What? Taken.
Taken? Is this a sea squirt?
Is this a sea squirt?
Was it the sea squirt you all ate?
No, definitely not. This is not sea squirt.
Probably not.
They all ate different things.
No, I thought so, but you said something about it melting, so I thought for sure it wouldn't melt.
No, but I'm having doubts.
I thought you landed on sea squirt.
I thought they were all different.I thought they were all different.
This is hard.
It's so hard.
I thought they weren't ascidians.
Because it's something completely different.
This is hard.
Because I thought I'd be fooled
When I tasted it and knew what it tasted like
I thought they were all different
I thought I'd landed on boiled ascidians.
It's so hard.
It's hard.
That's why
I'd like you all to try some of Hinoya Ishinomaki Mizusan's other canned goods.
Hinoya Ishinomaki Fisheries' other canned products.
I'd like to introduce Hoya to you
Once again...
Let's quickly forget about what just happened
I'm sure you'll understand.
We were really the first to eat
The canned sea squirt
We've landed on it.
I had some earlier.
It was so delicious!
It's the first time I've ever had it properly.
It was delicious.
And it was so big.
I was surprised, wasn't I?
I liked it.
My dad used to eat sea squirts as a snack.
He used to eat sea squirt as a snack.
I used to get some from him.
But the canned sea squirt was also very tasty.
The degree of change is just as it is.
I was surprised at how delicious it was.
At night, we would go out and peel the sea squirts
I got them at night, peeled them, and brought them in the morning.
They bring them in in the morning and can them right away.
And they can them right away.
You can eat it while it's still edible.
While it's still edible.
So it's really fresh.
It's really fresh.
So many people's hearts are in it.
Because it's packed with so many people's thoughts.
I want everyone to eat a lot of it.
I want people to eat a lot of it.
I heard there are a lot of recipes.
Doesn't this look delicious?
A side dish for takoyaki.
I'm sure it's delicious!
I heard it's also good mixed with sake.
I heard it's delicious.
I'd love for you all to try it.
I'd love it if you'd try it and comment on it in the comments section or something.
I'd love to try it when I'm over 20.
I'd like to try it when I'm over 20.
I'd like you to tell me about it.
And for those of you
I'd like you to teach me how to do it.
I heard that you can buy it on the Internet.
You can buy it on the Internet.
This hut.
And the three kinds of food we just ate.
I heard you can buy a lot of them.
They were all delicious.
I hope you'll check them out as well.
In the overview section
in the overview section.
Please check it out!
Thank you very much for today's video.
Thank you very much for watching today's video.
Please subscribe to our channel!
That's all for now.
Cloud Star Last!
Gunstar by Mr. Taoki out of the blue!
Thank you very much!